If I'd known it would end up like this…
ถ้าฉันรู้ว่ามันจะจบลงแบบนั้น…
I never would've taken the job.
ฉันคงไม่มีวันรับงานนั้น
I didn't like it from the start.
ฉันไม่ชอบงานนั้นตั้งแต่แรกแล้ว
It will be okay. Just take it easy.
นายจะไม่เป็นไรนะ อดทนไว้
It's not that bad. We'll be at the hospital soon.
มันไม่แย่ขนาดนั้นหรอก เดี๋ยวก็ถึงโรงพยาบาลแล้ว
I told you, no hospitals.
บอกแล้วไงว่าไม่ไปโรงพยาบาล
Get me to the doctor, not the hospital.
พาฉันไปหาหมอ ไม่ใช่ไปโรงพยาบาล
He's at Hellblau Hotel.
เขาอยู่ที่โรงแรมเฮลล์เบลา
Look, I know what you're thinking.
นี่ ฉันรู้นะว่านายคิดอะไรอยู่
If you go to the hospital, the cops will come and you'll go to prison again.
ถ้าไปโรงพยาบาล ตำรวจจะแห่มาและนายจะต้องติดคุกอีก
But we ain't got time to take you to that underground doc!
แต่เราไม่มีเวลาพานายไปหาหมอเถื่อนนั่นหรอก
Hellblau… Hotel!
โรงแรม… เฮลล์เบลา
Life's more important than prison! If--
ชีวิตสำคัญกว่าคุกนะ ถ้า…
Take me there now! Hellblau Hotel!
พาฉันไปเดี๋ยวนี้! โรงแรมเฮลล์เบลา!
I told you. There's always trouble when a woman's involved.
บอกแล้วไง มีผู้หญิงมาเกี่ยวข้องทีไร ก็วุ่นวายทุกที
I'm begging you… Get me to Dr. Tenma fast.
ขอร้องล่ะ รีบพาฉันไปหาหมอเท็นมะเถอะนะ
Make sure you're not rude.
รักษามารยาทด้วยนะ
The man you're about to meet
คนที่นายกำลังจะไปเจอ
isn't a person someone like you can normally meet.
ไม่ใช่คนที่นายจะเจอได้ทั่วไปนะ
I should've brought my autograph book for him to sign.
ผมน่าจะเอาสมุดมาขอลายเซ็นเขาด้วยนะเนี่ย
Screw around and I'll kill you.
ถ้าทำตัวไร้สาระ ฉันฆ่านายแน่
Come in.
เข้ามา
This is my man, Martin.
นี่ลูกน้องผมครับ ชื่อมาร์ติน
You can leave now.
นายไปได้แล้ว
What?
หา
I want to speak with him privately.
ฉันอยากคุยกับเขาเป็นการส่วนตัว
All right.
ได้ครับ
If you screw things up, I really will kill you.
ถ้านายทำเสียเรื่อง ฉันจะฆ่านายจริงๆ
Can I sit here?
นั่งตรงนี้ได้ไหมครับ
Go ahead.
เอาเลย
How many years have you been working for The Baby?
ทำงานให้เบบี้มากี่ปีแล้ว
I guess it's been three years now.
น่าจะสามปีแล้วละครับ
And before that?
แล้วก่อนหน้านั้นล่ะ
Prison, huh? How many years?
ติดคุกเหรอ กี่ปี
Eight years.
แปดปีครับ
-For murder? -Yes.
- ข้อหาฆาตกรรมเหรอ - ใช่ครับ
You got out pretty quick for murder.
ถือว่าออกมาเร็วมากนะสำหรับข้อหาฆาตกรรม
I was a model inmate.
ผมเป็นนักโทษชั้นดีน่ะครับ
I hear you're a model employee too.
ได้ยินมาว่านายเป็นลูกจ้างชั้นดีด้วยเหมือนกัน
I'll do anything, whatever the job is. However…
ผมทำทุกอย่างแหละครับ ไม่ว่างานอะไร แต่ว่า…
"However"?
"แต่ว่า" เหรอ
I don't like jobs that involve women.
ผมไม่ชอบงานที่เกี่ยวข้องกับผู้หญิง
I see.
อ่อ
I won't say no to work.
ผมจะไม่ปฏิเสธงานหรอกนะครับ
But I just don't like getting involved with women.
แต่ผมแค่ไม่ชอบยุ่งเกี่ยวกับผู้หญิง
This involves a woman.
เรื่องนี้เกี่ยวกับผู้หญิง
I want you to look after a certain woman for a while.
ฉันอยากให้นายดูแลผู้หญิงคนนึงสักพัก
What a lousy job.
เป็นงานที่โคตรกากเลย
I want you to go to Düsseldorf and bring a certain woman here.
ฉันอยากให้นายไปดึสเซิลดอร์ฟ และพาผู้หญิงคนนึงมาที่นี่
Since you don't like getting involved with women,
เพราะนายไม่ชอบยุ่งเกี่ยวกับผู้หญิง
you're perfect for this job.
นายเลยเหมาะกับงานนี้มาก
I know you'll treat this job in a business-like fashion.
ฉันรู้ว่านายจะทำงานนี้ด้วยวิธีแบบธุรกิจ
Eva Heinemann?
คุณเอวา ไฮเนมันน์ใช่ไหม
Who are you?
นายเป็นใคร
Martin. But my name doesn't matter.
มาร์ตินครับ แต่ชื่อผมไม่สำคัญหรอก
I was told to bring you to Frankfurt.
ผมได้รับคำสั่งให้พาคุณไปแฟรงก์เฟิร์ต
By whom?
ใครสั่ง
A man wearing glasses and a high-class suit.
ผู้ชายใส่แว่นและสูทหรู
A man wearing glasses?
ผู้ชายใส่แว่นเหรอ
He's not one of Roberto's men, right?
เขาไม่ใช่คนของโรแบร์โต้ใช่ไหม
I'm not sure.
เรื่องนั้นผมไม่แน่ใจ
But he's a big shot.
แต่เขาเป็นคนมีอิทธิพล
I won't force you if you don't want to.
ผมจะไม่บังคับคุณถ้าคุณไม่อยากไป
I'm not too thrilled about this either.
ผมก็ไม่ได้ตื่นเต้นกับเรื่องนี้เท่าไหร่เหมือนกัน
Someone is after me right now.
ตอนนี้มีคนตามล่าฉันอยู่
Really?
งั้นเหรอ
Will you be my bodyguard?
นายเป็นบอดี้การ์ดให้ฉันได้ไหม
Well, that is part of this job.
นั่นเป็นส่วนนึงของงานนี้อยู่แล้วครับ
Wait there.
รอตรงนี้นะ
Carry this.
ถือนี่
Let's go. This is better than getting killed by that man.
ไปกันเถอะ ยังไงแบบนี้ก็ดีกว่าโดนผู้ชายคนนั้นฆ่า
What a pain in the ass.
น่ารำคาญชะมัด
The way she swings her hips and the smell of her perfume…
วิธีที่เธอส่ายสะโพกและกลิ่นน้ำหอมของเธอ…
It's ticking me off.
มันทำให้ฉันหงุดหงิด
What a lousy job.
เป็นงานที่โคตรกากเลย
Why don't you talk?
ทำไมไม่คุยเลยล่ะ
Well, if you'd like, I can talk about something.
ถ้าคุณอยากคุย ผมก็คุยได้นะ
I don't want to talk.
ฉันไม่อยากคุยหรอก
Then let's not talk.
งั้นก็ไม่ต้องคุยกันครับ
Any liquor?
มีเหล้าไหม
Don't you have any liquor?
ไม่มีเหล้าเหรอ
Sorry, but I don't drink.
ขอโทษนะครับ แต่ผมไม่ดื่ม
I'll check out the dining car.
ฉันจะไปดูตู้เสบียงนะ
Is that right? You're traveling on your own.
ใช่ไหมครับ คุณเดินทางคนเดียว
I happen to be traveling alone too.
บังเอิญผมก็เดินทางคนเดียวเหมือนกัน
Say, why don't you tell me where you'll be staying?
งั้นบอกผมได้ไหมครับว่าคุณจะพักที่ไหน
Here's my business--
นี่นามบัตร…
The hell are you doing?
ทำบ้าอะไรของแก
Me? She asked me for a drink.
ฉันเหรอ เธอขอเครื่องดื่มฉันน่ะ
Don't lay a hand on this woman.
อย่ายุ่งกับผู้หญิงคนนี้
Why do you eat in silence?
ทำไมถึงกินไม่พูดไม่จาเลยล่ะ
Like I said before, I'll talk if you like.
อย่างที่บอก ผมจะคุยถ้าคุณอยากคุย
Why don't you drink liquor?
ทำไมนายถึงไม่ดื่มเหล้าล่ะ
My mom was a horrible alcoholic.
แม่ผมติดเหล้าหนักมากน่ะ
But you can drink if you like.
แต่ถ้าคุณอยากดื่มก็ดื่มได้นะ
I bet your mom had a good reason for drinking.
ฉันเชื่อว่าแม่นายคงมีเหตุผลที่ดีในการดื่มแน่ๆ
Do you think so?
คุณคิดอย่างนั้นเหรอ
I sure do.
ใช่
You see, I have a very good reason for my drinking.
ฉันเองก็มีเหตุผลที่ดีมากในการดื่มเหมือนกัน
Go ahead. Please tell me. If you hate eating in silence, that is.
งั้นก็เล่ามาสิครับ ถ้าคุณไม่ชอบกินข้าวแบบเงียบๆ ก็เล่าเลย
It's a long story.
เรื่องมันยาวน่ะ
That's fine. Tell it.
ไม่เป็นไรครับ เล่าเถอะ
I once had a fiancé.
ฉันเคยมีคู่หมั้น
He was a Japanese surgeon.
เขาเป็นศัลยแพทย์ชาวญี่ปุ่น
He was an extremely gifted surgeon.
เขาเป็นศัลยแพทย์ที่มีพรสวรรค์มาก
And then…
จากนั้น…
And then I tried to shoot and kill my ex-fiancé.
จากนั้นฉันก็พยายามจะยิงอดีตคู่หมั้นฉันให้ตาย
Does that surprise you?
อึ้งไหมล่ะ
I tried to kill that guy!
ฉันพยายามฆ่าไอ้หมอนั่นอะ!
But you didn't shoot him.
แต่คุณก็ไม่ได้ยิงเขา
Compared to my story, that's a lot better.
เทียบกับเรื่องของผมแล้ว เรื่องของคุณดีกว่าเยอะเลย
What's your story?
เรื่องของนายเป็นยังไง
Tell me.
เล่ามาซิ
I shot them.
ผมยิงพวกเขา
My woman, who was screwing another man in our bedroom,
แฟนผม ที่กำลังเอากับชายอื่นในห้องนอนของเรา
and the man as well. I shot them until I ran out of bullets.
และยิงไอ้ผู้ชายคนนั้นด้วย ผมยิงพวกเขาจนกระสุนหมดแม็ก
The room was filled with the smell of her blood,
ในห้องเต็มไปด้วยกลิ่นเลือดของเธอ
the smell of his blood and, the smell of perfume.
กลิ่นเลือดของเขา และกลิ่นน้ำหอม
When I came to my senses, I was standing there by myself.
พอผมรู้สึกตัว ผมก็ยืนอยู่ตรงนั้นคนเดียว
You sure are an idiot.
นายนี่มันโง่จริงๆ
That's for sure.
จริงครับ
What a lousy job.
เป็นงานที่โคตรกากเลย
My employer is waiting inside this hotel.
เจ้านายผมรออยู่ในโรงแรมนี้
You're a murderer, right?
นายเป็นฆาตกรไม่ใช่เหรอ
Don't touch me.
อย่ามาแตะต้องฉัน
What room?
ห้องอะไร
I'll take you there.
เดี๋ยวผมพาคุณไปเอง
You're not dressed appropriately to enter this hotel.
นายแต่งตัวไม่เหมาะที่จะเข้าไปในโรงแรมนี้
You can wait here.
รอที่นี่ก็ได้
Room 1014.
ห้อง 1014 ครับ
What a bitch.
ร้ายกาจชะมัด
I don't know what the man in glasses wants from that woman,
ไม่รู้ว่าผู้ชายใส่แว่นต้องการอะไรจากผู้หญิงคนนั้น
but if she turns him down,
แต่ถ้าเธอปฏิเสธเขา
this lousy job will be over and I won't have to see that woman again.
งานกากๆ นี่ก็จะจบลง และฉันจะไม่ต้องเจอผู้หญิงคนนั้นอีก
What's wrong? You're looking a little pale.
เป็นอะไรไปครับ หน้าคุณดูซีดๆ นะ
It was an acceptable deal.
มันเป็นข้อตกลงที่ยอมรับได้
I can use this card all I like.
ฉันใช้การ์ดใบนี้ได้ตามใจชอบ
What are you waiting for? We're going.
รออะไรอยู่ล่ะ เราจะไปกันแล้ว
Going where?
ไปไหนครับ
Shopping.
ไปช็อปปิ้งน่ะสิ
This is a lousy job.
เป็นงานที่โคตรกากเลย
This is the next place.
นี่แหละคือที่ต่อไป
That's a men's clothing store.
นั่นร้านเสื้อผ้าผู้ชายนี่ครับ
I need you to wear something proper.
ฉันอยากให้นายแต่งตัวดีๆ หน่อย
I'm fine like this.
ผมโอเคกับการแต่งตัวแบบนี้
I don't like it.
ฉันไม่ชอบ
I won't have the man I'm with dressed like a bum.
ฉันจะไม่ยอมให้ผู้ชายที่ฉันอยู่ด้วย แต่งตัวเหมือนขอทานหรอก
I'll take this.
เอาชุดนี้ค่ะ
And a necktie.
และเน็กไทเส้นนึง
Kenzo…
เคนโซ…
Try these on.
ลองใส่เสื้อผ้าพวกนี้ซิ
A necktie, huh? This blows.
เน็กไทเนี่ยนะ โคตรเห่ย
-How is it? -Well…
- เป็นไงบ้าง - ก็…
Nice. You're looking better.
ดีนะ นายดูดีขึ้น
But fix that necktie.
แต่ผูกเน็กไทนั่นใหม่ซะ
Quit swaggering your shoulders like some mobster when you walk.
เลิกเดินวางก้ามเหมือนนักเลงได้แล้ว
I'm just walking normally.
ผมก็แค่เดินตามปกตินะ
Normal for you isn't normal.
ปกติสำหรับนายมันไม่ปกติเลย
From now on, you need to protect me.
จากนี้ไป นายต้องปกป้องฉัน
No matter where we go,
ไม่ว่าเราจะไปที่ไหน
I need you to act in a way that won't disgrace me.
ฉันอยากให้นายไม่ทำตัวให้ฉันต้องอับอายขายหน้า
That's your job, right?
นั่นคืองานของนายใช่ไหมล่ะ
That's right. That is my job.
ครับ นั่นคืองานของผม
Get your elbows off the table.
เอาศอกลงจากโต๊ะ
Use your fork with your left and your knife with your right.
จับส้อมด้วยมือซ้าย จับมีดด้วยมือขวา
Don't make noise when you eat.
เวลากินอย่าเคี้ยวเสียงดังสิ
So, I guess it's true.
สงสัยจะจริงแฮะ
What is?
เรื่องอะไร
Your story.
เรื่องคุณน่ะครับ
About you being the classy daughter of a hospital director.
เรื่องที่คุณเป็นคุณหนู ลูกสาวของผู้อำนวยการโรงพยาบาล
You thought I was lying?
นายคิดว่าฉันโกหกเหรอ
Until I brought you to this city, you looked like just some alcoholic woman.
ก่อนจะพาคุณมาเมืองนี้ คุณดูเหมือนผู้หญิงติดเหล้าคนนึง
What about now?
แล้วตอนนี้ล่ะ
You're a classy woman.
คุณเป็นผู้หญิงมีระดับ
This is my true form.
นี่คือรูปแบบที่แท้จริงของฉัน
Eva Heinemann has returned to where she belongs.
เอวา ไฮเนมันน์กลับมาในที่ที่เหมาะกับเธอแล้ว
What's that?
นั่นอะไรครับ
A party invitation.
บัตรเชิญงานเลี้ยง
-A party? -That's right.
- งานเลี้ยงเหรอ - ใช่
This is the job I was given.
นี่คืองานที่ฉันได้รับมอบหมายมา
A job?
งานเหรอ
I'm supposed to attend several parties.
ฉันต้องไปงานเลี้ยงหลายงานเลย
That's all.
แค่นั้นแหละ
You must be glad. That sounds like a fun job.
คุณคงดีใจนะครับ ฟังดูเป็นงานที่สนุกทีเดียว
You're coming with me.
นายต้องไปกับฉัน
You'll play the part of a man who's worthy of escorting me.
นายจะรับบทเป็นผู้ชายที่คู่ควรแก่การปกป้องฉัน
This job's just getting lousier.
งานนี้ชักจะกากขึ้นเรื่อยๆ แล้ว
How does it feel finally being back on your home turf?
รู้สึกยังไงบ้างครับ ที่ในที่สุดก็ได้กลับมาบ้านเกิด
What could be so damn funny?
ขำเรื่องอะไรขนาดนั้นนะ
What the hell do these people here talk about anyway?
ว่าแต่คนที่นี่เขาคุยเรื่องอะไรกัน
About the weather? What about stocks?
เรื่องดินฟ้าอากาศเหรอ แล้วหุ้นล่ะ
I don't even know what language they're speaking.
ฉันไม่รู้ด้วยซ้ำว่าพวกเขาพูดภาษาอะไรกัน
This is making me nauseous.
เห็นแล้วคลื่นไส้ชะมัด
So, there you are.
อยู่นี่เอง
Never mind me. You have fun.
ผมต้องสนผมหรอก คุณสนุกอยู่นี่
-We're going. -Huh?
- เราจะไปกันแล้ว - หา
We're leaving.
เราจะกลับกันแล้ว
Hold on!
เดี๋ยวสิครับ
He wasn't at this party.
เขาไม่ได้อยู่ที่งานเลี้ยงนี้
My job is done.
งานฉันเสร็จแล้ว
Who's not here?
ใครไม่อยู่ครับ
Take me away.
พาฉันไปที
Take me anywhere. Just get me out of here fast!
พาฉันไปไหนก็ได้ แค่รีบพาฉันไปจากที่นี่ก็พอ
Her hand was trembling…
มือเธอสั่น…
but I didn't know why at the time.
แต่ตอนนั้นฉันไม่รู้ว่าเพราะอะไร
I survived the day.
วันนี้ฉันรอดมาได้
What's the matter?
มีอะไรเหรอครับ
I thought you'd returned to where you belong.
ผมนึกว่าคุณจะกลับไป อยู่ในที่ที่เหมาะกับคุณซะอีก
I used to live that kind of life every day.
ฉันเคยใช้ชีวิตแบบนั้นทุกวัน
I thought if I returned to that world that my true self would return.
ฉันเคยคิดว่าถ้าฉันกลับไปโลกแบบนั้นอีก ตัวตนที่แท้จริงของฉันจะกลับมา
But now, a bar like this is the only place you feel at home, huh?
แต่ตอนนี้ บาร์แบบนี้ เป็นที่เดียวที่คุณรู้สึกเหมือนอยู่บ้านใช่ไหม
This isn't where I belong either!
นี่ก็ไม่ใช่ที่ที่เหมาะกับฉันเหมือนกัน
Not here! Not there either!
ไม่ใช่ที่นี่ ที่นั่นก็ไม่ใช่
There is no place where I belong! I already knew that!
ไม่มีที่ไหนที่เหมาะกับฉันเลย ฉันรู้อยู่แล้วละ
You know, when this job is over, I'm sure I'll be murdered.
รู้ไหม พอจบงานนี้แล้ว ฉันมั่นใจว่าฉันจะถูกฆ่า
I thought it would be better than being killed by Roberto in Düsseldorf
ฉันเคยคิดว่ามันจะดีกว่า โดนโรแบร์โต้ฆ่าตายในดึสเซิลดอร์ฟ
where I was a total mess.
ที่สภาพฉันดูไม่ได้
I thought it would be better to be killed as the beautiful Eva Heinemann.
ฉันคิดว่ามันจะดีกว่า ถ้าโดนฆ่าในฐานะเอวา ไฮเนมันน์คนสวย
But when you die…
แต่พอคนเราตาย…
it's all the same.
มันก็เหมือนกันหมด
I wanted to protect her.
ฉันอยากปกป้องเธอ
That's a bad habit of mine.
นั่นเป็นนิสัยที่ไม่ดีของฉัน
Out of the blue, I suddenly wanted to protect this woman.
อยู่ๆ ฉันก็รู้สึกอยากปกป้องผู้หญิงคนนี้
Christ! How the hell did this happen anyway?
ให้ตายสิ ว่าแต่มันเกิดขึ้นได้ยังไงเนี่ย
That's why… we're going to Dr. Tenma… so I can tell him.
เพราะอย่างนั้นแหละ… เราจะไปหาหมอเท็นมะ ฉันจะได้บอกเขาได้
Hang in there! Just a little longer! We're almost there!
อดทนไว้นะ อีกนิดเดียว ใกล้ถึงแล้ว
A necktie…
เน็กไท…
If it hadn't been for this…
ถ้าไม่ใช่เพราะไอ้นี่…
I never would've been there.
ฉันคงไม่มีวันไปที่นั่น
I never would've seen…
ฉันคงไม่ต้องเห็น…
such terror.
ความน่ากลัวขนาดนั้น